svnforum.org 2015-06-05

# Privacy Policy | WANdisco

### Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting WANdisco.com, a WANdisco, Inc. site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at our sites.

### The Information We Collect

At our site, you may order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in an online forum or community. The types of personally identifiable information th at may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At certain parts of our site, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to view information, order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

### How We Use The Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of WANdisco, Inc. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for WANdisco, Inc.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this site.

Finally, WANdisco, Inc. sites covered by this Privacy Notice will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

### Collection Of Information By Third-Parties And Sponsors

Our site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

### Cookies

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), and save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

### Our Commitment To Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

### Our Trademarks

WANdisco has registered the trademarks below or has otherwise sought protection as indicated below in the U.S and other countries. We have done this to protect and preserve the marks for our community of customers, developers, partners, and supporters for the benefit of everyone involved with WANdisco. By this we mean that people should be able to recognize when a product is from WANdisco.

You may use the WANdisco trademarks below in any blog, news article, or on your website without our written consent, as long as you use them according to this guideline, retain the capitalization structure indicated below, and retain the © symbol or ™ symbol as applicable on the right shoulder of the mark according to the usage in the list below.

##### Term

| 

##### Status

| 

##### Use  
  
---|---|---  
WANdisco  |  ®  |  Computer software company, logo and its products / services   
SmartSVN  |  ®  |   
We Make Software Happen  |  ®  |   
We Make Software Possible  |  ®  |   
uberSVN  |  ®  |  Open Application Lifecycle Management Platform for Subversion   
UberAPPS  |  ®  |   
Nonstop NameNode  |  ™  |   
Non-stop NameNode  |  ™  |   
Nonstop Data  |  ™  |   
Non-stop Data  |  ™  |   
Altostor  |  ™  |   
SVN MS  |  ™  |   
SVN MS Plus  |  ™  |   
Continuous Availability  |  ™  |   
The Power of 100%  |  ™  |   
  
### How You Can Access Or Correct Information

Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our site may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of collection. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our site go back to that portion of the site to review the information you provided.

You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for said service.

4847 Hopyard Road, Suite 4-208  
Pleasanton, CA 94588, USA  
+1 (866) 846-0404 (voice)  
+1 (866) 247 7584 (fax) 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the WANdisco, Inc. online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@wandisco.com](mailto:privacy@wandisco.com).
